Guide to the Stanford University, Centennial Office, Records
Stanford University Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1991-173
  - Commencement Memos (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Financial Records (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Centennial Enhancements (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Centennial Memorabilia (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Centennial Year Baccalaureate Service (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Diploma Copy (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Display Holder (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Centennial Year Commencement Program (2 copies) (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Stadium Finale - Eventure (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
  - Stadium Event Producers - Madison Square Garden (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Stadium Event Producers - USA Productions (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Stadium Event Producers - Eventure (Box 37, Folder 5-6)
  - Stadium Event Producers - Selection Process (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Stadium Show Script, Apr 1991 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Stadium Show Script, Jul 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Stadium Show (Box 37, Folder 10-12)
  - Centennial Stadium Spectacular (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Hospital Logotype (Box 37, Folder 14-15)
  - Logo and Memorabilia (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
  - Stickers (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Centennial, General (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Centennial Personal and Vehicle Passes (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Centennial Memorabilia (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Centennial Programs (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Communications Plan (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Participants in the Centennial Roundtables (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Centennial Fanfare (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Centennial Convocation Program (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Centennial Finale Slides (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - ASSU Centennial Commission 1985 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Centennial Medallions (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Centennial Parade in Palo Alto (Box 38, Folder 16-17)
  - Trustees - Centennial Participation (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - DAPER - Centennial (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Centennial Year Board Presentation, Apr 1991 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Quilt (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - CCRMA and Winton Marsalis (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
  - Proclamations - Stanford Centennial (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Centennial Commissions (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Student Participation in Centennial (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Centennial Facilities Construction Projects (Box 39, Folder 10-11)
  - Facilities Calendar, Sep 18 to Sep 27, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Facilities Calendar, Sep 28 to Oct 17, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Gold Spike Celebration, May 1991 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Yell Leaders (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - PACE and the Campaign for Stanford (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Trowel (Box 39, Folder 17-19)
  - Booklet: The Stanford Museum Centennial Handbook (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Poolaw Photo Exhibit, Oct 1990 (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
  - Seismic work on Main Quad Portals (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Daily Dining and Entertainment Guide (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Ticketing / Credentialing (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Staff, Student Ticketing (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Volunteering / Incentives (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Friends of Stanford Support Groups (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Festival of Thanksgiving (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Press Center (Box 40, Folder 11-13)
  - Congratulations from Case Western Reserve University (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Congratulations from The White House (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Publicity Expenses (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Community Relations (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - The Capsule Ceremony (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Special Situations Registrations (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Dean of Student Affairs (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Haas Center (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Institutes and Centers (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Outside Services (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Leadership Forums (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Roundtable Speakers Dinner (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Oak Planting Event (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Historical Society Public School Program (Box 41, Folder 5-6)
  - Red Barn Dedication, Oct 5, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Community Report, Spring 1986 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Community Report, Spring 1987 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Observer Special Issue, April 1987 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - President Rhodes of Cornell (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Kile Ozier (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Don Fehrenbacher Working File (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Visit with George Shultz, 1988-04 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Lois Stolz (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Dan Carlson Article (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Senator Timothy Wirth (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Audiovisual material
    - "The Human Genome Project", 2 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - "The Information Explosion", 2 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - "Ethnicity, Equity and Environment", 2 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Stanford Quartet commercials, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - KCBS, Jim Taylor, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Centennial spots, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Sunset Dinner, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - "Making History Again", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Roundtable "Advances and Ethical Choices", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Roundtable "Ethnic Diversity", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Roundtable "Values", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Roundtable "Saving the Planet", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Stephen Jay Gould, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Ken Arrow interview, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Durham interview, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Paul Berg interview, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Reading of Jane Stanford's address to the Board of Trustees (1903), 1911; 43.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (DAT) (Box 43)
    - Roundtable "The Arts" (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Roundtable "Moving the 21st Century into the classroom", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Roundtable "A New World Order", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Roundtable "Forging New Alliances", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - "Harvard 350th Anniversary Celebration", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Smithsonian "American Dream at Groton", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - "Stanford, A Sentimental Journey", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - "Making History Again", 1 video reel(s) (1 inch) (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - "Stanford, A Sentimental Journey", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - "Mexican President at Stanford, Governor Wilson faces protests at Stanford", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - "Stanford Centennial" by Mick Lerner, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - "Stanford at Fairmont" tape #1, 1 videotape(s) (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - "Stanford at Fairmont" tape #2, 1 videotape(s) (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - "Stanford at Fairmont" tape #3, 1 videotape(s) (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - "Stanford at Fairmont" tape #4, 1 videotape(s) (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - "Stanford at Fairmont" tape #5, 1 videotape(s) (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #1, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #2, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #3, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #4, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #5, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #6, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #7, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #8, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #9, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #10, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #11, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #12, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #13, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #14, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #15, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #16, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #17, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #18, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #19, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - "San Francisco Centennial", tape #20, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1991-183
  - General Files, Subseries 1
    - "When We Were Fifty" (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Planning, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - KRON-TV's Centennial Program, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Dinner Meeting, May 20, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Subcommittee on 1988-1990 Centennial Planning, Jun 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Now Through 1987 Group, Jun 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Gorbachev: Translators / Interpreters (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - Gorbachev: Organization (Box 1, Folder 9-11)
    - Gorbachev: Speech, Jun 4, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Gorbachev -- Schultz Discussion, Jun 4, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Gorbachev News Reports, May 29, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Gorbachev News Reports, May 30, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Gorbachev News Reports, May 31, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Gorbachev News Reports, Jun 4, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Gorbachev News Reports, Jun 5, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Gorbachev News Reports, Jun 6, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Proposals and Projects, Master List (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The Stanford Album (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
    - Miscellaneous Proposals to the Centennial Operating Committee (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
    - Centennial Funded Projects (Box 2, Folder 6-14)
    - Centennial 100 (Box 3, Folder 1-5)
    - Project Diversity 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Black Engineering Students Conference 1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Solar Car Project (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Symposium: Switzerland in a Changing World (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Conference: Talking Terrorism (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Symposium: Understanding Origin (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Vaughn Institute Workshop on Homer and Linear B (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Vengeance Colloquium (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Conference: Writing / Ecriture / Schrift (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Conference: You Can Make a Difference (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - CCRMA / Marsalis: Computer Ja (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    - CEPR: Tax and Budget Policy for the '90s (Box 4, Folder 5-9)
    - Chronotypes: The Construction of Time (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - CTV Technology and Cultural Design Exhibition (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Civil Engineering Centennial Celebration (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - College Board Colloquium (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Creative Writing Press / Promotion (Box 4, Folder 14-15)
    - Creative Writing (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
    - Double Jeopardy Conference (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    - Durham Symposium (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
    - Freud Conference (Box 5, Folder 8-11)
    - Day in the Life of Stanford (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Diebenkorn Exhibit (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Disability Institute (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cultural Nationalism Conference (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Culture Fest (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Culture, Gender and Social Movements of the 1960s (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Educating Children at Risk (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
    - Future is Now, Voices for Children (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Arts and Education Conference (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Large-Scale Physics Workshop (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Building a Safer 21st Century (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
    - Caricatures Exhibition (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Summer Performing Arts Festival (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Teaching Week (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Tree of Peace Ceremony (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Volunteers in Asia -- 25th Anniversary Reunion (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Centennial Multi-Image Show (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Commonwealth Club Event (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Computer Science Department 25th Anniversary (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Applied Physics 25th Anniversary (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Berlin OS East-West Event (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Bing School 25th Anniversary (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
    - Bloch Centennial Celebration (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Artists in New York, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Stanford String Quartet Tour (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
    - Savoyards, Yeoman of the Guard (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Black Theater: Moving Toward the 21st Century (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Stanford String Quartet Tour Promotion (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
    - Stanford Symphony Orchestra Tour (Box 8, Folder 4-6)
    - Book: "Stanford String Quartet Tour" (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Postal Card Ceremony Press Kit (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Commemorative Postcard (Box 8, Folder 9-11)
    - Centennial Celebration Committee Report, Jun 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Inaugural Session of the Centennial Operating Committee, Oct 1, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Operation Committee Meetings
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Oct 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Nov-Dec 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Jan-Feb 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Mar-Apr 1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, May-Aug 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Sep-Oct 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Nov-Dec 1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Jan 14, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Mar 1988 (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Apr 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings May-Aug 1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings Sep 1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings Oct 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings Dec 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Jan 1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Feb 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, May 9, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, May 30, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Oct-Dec 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Jan 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meeting, Apr 10, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, May-Jul 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Sep-Oct 1990 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Nov-Dec 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, Feb-Apr 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Centennial Operating Committee Meetings, May-Dec 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Centennial Operating Committee 1986-1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Centennial Year Presentation, Apr 8, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Symposia Planning Committee 1989 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
    - Creative Task Force 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Communications Task Force 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Protocol Task Force (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Centennial Publications (Box 11, Folder 11-13)
    - Book, "Centennial Conference Room Calendar" 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Centennial TV Spots (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    - Approaching Stanford (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
    - Correspondence of Dave Ream, Public Affairs 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
    - Correspondence of Dave Ream, Public Affairs 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Jerry Lieberman Correspondence, written by Stephen Peeps, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Apr-Jun 1986 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Jul-Dec 1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Jan-Jun 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Jul-Dec 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Mar 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Apr 1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, May-Aug 1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Sep-Nov 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Jan-Feb 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Mar 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Apr 1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, May-Jul 1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Aug 1990 (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Sep 1990 (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Oct 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Nov 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Dec 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Jan-Feb 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Mar 1991 (Box 14, Folder 7-9)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Apr 1991 (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, May 1991 (Box 14, Folder 12-14)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Jun 1991 (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Jul 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Aug 1991 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Sep 1991 (Box 15, Folder 7-9)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Oct-Nov 1991 (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
      - Correspondence of Stephen Peeps, Dec 1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Centennial Year Managers Meeting Notes (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
    - Centennial Year Managers, Opening Week (Box 16, Folder 3-5)
    - Centennial Year Managers, Project Assignments (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Centennial Year Managers, Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Centennial Year Managers, Finale Weekend (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
    - Registration Company Search (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
    - Convocation Red Book (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Centennial Convocation, Sep 29, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Centennial Convocation, Sep 30, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Centennial Convocation, Oct 1, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Convocation letters to Richard Lyman, Aug-Sep 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Convocation Letters to/from University Presidents (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Letters on Flags used in Convocation (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Convocation Invitations to Foreign Consulates (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
    - Letters from Foreign Consulates about the Convocation (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Follow-up Letters to Foreign Consulates (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Letters from Harvard and Indiana, Sep 1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Convocation Working File (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
    - Convocation Organization, Carillon - Dances (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Convocation Organization, Performing Arts - Welcome Back (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Convocation Organization, Dinners - Parking and Transportation (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Facilities Schedule for Convocation (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
    - Biographies of Convocation Participants (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Flower (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Teaching Assistants (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Quilt (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Centennial Logo (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Advertisements (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Centennial Vendor Kit (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Sequoia Centennial Issue 1986 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Centennial Announcements (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Alumni Association (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Instructional Television Network 1987 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Stanford Clinic Employee Awards Banquet (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Stanford Heritage (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Stanford Humanities Review (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Stanford in 3-D (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Stanford Magazine, Pre-Centennial Issue (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Altenberg: Stanford's Forgotten Vision (Box 18, Folder 17-18)
    - Antique Clothing (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Cedro House Reunion (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Earth Sciences Alumni Day and Directory (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Foreign Scholars (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Cornell University (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Sigourney Weaver (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Student / Staff Directory (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Jasper Ridge, A Stanford Sanctuary (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Powwow, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - SEAS Environmental Audit, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
    - Sigma Chi Centennial, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Ujamaa Archives (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Cornerstone: Stanford Historical Society (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - John Steinbeck Arthurian Society (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Book: "Herder Today" (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Booklet "Carlos Salinas de Gortari" (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Booklet "Centennial Year Commencement Exercises" (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Magazine "California History", Fall 1991 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - 5 Stanford TV spots, 1990; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - "Stanford - A Place in History", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - "Horace Poolaw Photography Project", 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Year Managers post-Finale de-briefing, 4 audiocassette(s) (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - "Wattis Rm Audio Trans", 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Album from International Centennial Celebrations in Mexico City, Toronto, and Hong Kong, 1990 [signatures of honored speakers and attendees] (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Project and Proposal Files, Subseries 2
    - Galarza Lectures: 1987 and 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Gondoliers [Stanford Savoyards] (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Hanna House 50th Anniversary (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Henricks photography project 1989-90 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Herder Conference 1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Herder Proceedings (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Heritage Center 1988 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Herpesvirus Workshop 1989-91 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - High Technology and the Americas 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Honoring 100 Years of Staff Diversity 1991-92 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Hoover Archives Exhibit (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Human Biology: the Challenge for 2005. 1989-90 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Humanities Ctr. 10th Anniversary, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - International Centennial Celebration: general file, 1988-89 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - International Centennial Celebration: London, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - International Centennial Celebration: London: Press, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - International Centennial Celebration: Mexico 1990 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - International Centennial Celebration: Mexico: Press (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - International Centennial Celebration: Toronto 1989-90 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - International Centennial Celebration: Toronto: Press (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - International Centennial Celebration: Hong Kong 1990 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - International Centennial Celebration: Hong Kong: Press (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Identity, Politics and Culture (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - International Center Booklet (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - International Festival (Box 22, Folder 25)